Hi, in this lesson I will quickly walk you through what you need to follow along with the course
and the good news is that the requirements are very simple. You do not need any previous
experience with Google Antigravity or other artificial intelligence tools. You also do not need
any prior experience with artificial intelligence powered integrated development environments.
We will start completely from scratch and explore Antigravity's step-by-step together,
so you can simply watch, follow along and learn as we go.
It is helpful if you have a basic understanding of JavaScript, but it is not required.
You will still be able to follow the lessons and see how everything works in practice.
Even if you are new to JavaScript or programming in general,
and that is it for the course requirements. If you are ready, let us move on and start learning
with Google Antigravity.